// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "_ skills can help you avoid conflict and solve problem.",
    answer: "communications",
    options: [
      "communications",
      "context",
      "purpose",
      "speech"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A highest form os communication, identified as fixed speech.",
    answer: "frozen",
    options: [
      "formal",
      "casual",
      "frozen",
      "consultative"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It employs a free and easy participation of both the speaker and listener.",
    answer: "casual",
    options: [
      "formal",
      "intimate",
      "frozen",
      "casual"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It is called as unplanned speech because it allows the speaker to use the participation and feedback if the listener.",
    answer: "consultative",
    options: [
      "formal",
      "frozen",
      "consultative",
      "casual"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "it is a private and practiced in dialogs between very close individuals leading to a high chance of nonverbal communication.",
    answer: "intimate",
    options: [
    "casual",
    "intimate",
    "formal",
    "frozen"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "It us used normally in writing rather than in speaking, thus, eliciting a mire formal kind of speech.",
  answer: "formal",
  options: [
    "casual",
    "formal",
    "frozen",
    "intimate"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "It is used when something set up as an object or and to be attained.",
  answer: "purpose",
  options: [
    "audience",
    "context",
    "purpose",
    "writing"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "A group if listeners or spectators.",
  answer: "audience",
  options: [
    "audience",
    "context",
    "purpose",
    "writing"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "The parts of a discourse that surround a word or passenger and can throw light or its meaning.",
  answer: "context",
  options: [
    "audience",
    "context",
    "purpose",
    "writing"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "it is a form language that the speaker employs according to the level of formality.",
  answer: "speech style",
  options: [
  "speech style",
  "purpose",
  "communication style",
  "context"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 11,
  question: "Speech style us identified into...",
  answer: "five",
  options: [
    "four",
    "six",
    "fire ",
    "three"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 12,
  question: "It is specific in form as it uses complex grammatic sentence structure and vocabulary known as expert in a particular field",
  answer: "frozen",
  options: [
    "formal",
    "intimate",
    "consultative",
    "frozen"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 13,
  question: "it is bidirectional or sometimes multi-directional in nature wherein the speakers supplies the necessary information and the listener participates continuously.",
  answer: "consultative",
  options: [
    "frozen",
    "consultative",
    "intimate",
    "formal"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "It is also called informal style since it is common among peers and friends.",
  answer: "casual",
  options: [
    "casual",
    "intimate",
    "formal",
    "frozen"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Can be used in writing, text messaging, email, or online chats with close family members and close friends.",
  answer: "intimate",
  options: [
    "formal",
    "frozen",
    "casual",
    "intimate"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 16,
  question: "Can also be used in writing text message, email, or online chat.",
  answer: "casual",
  options: [
    "formal",
    "intimate",
    "casual",
    "frozen"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 17,
  question: "typically used in unidirectional and informative, but just pure information can sometimes be dull, therefore it's occasionally persuasive too.",
  answer: "formal",
  options: [
    "formal",
    "frozen",
    "intimate",
    "casual"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 18,
  question: "This does involve a give-and-take communication, making this unidirectional.",
  answer: "frozen",
  options: [
    "intimate",
    "consultative",
    "casual",
    "frozen"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 19,
  question: "It is similar to casual style, it is also employs free and easy participation of both the speaker and the listener.",
  answer: "intimate",
  options: [
    "consultative",
    "intimate",
    "frozen",
    "casual"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 20,
  question: "It is use in ellipsis, contraction, and qualifying adverbials is eliminated.",
  answer: "formal",
  options: [
    "formal",
    "intimate",
    "casual",
    "consultative"
  ]
},
// you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];